(Howard:)Oh, before I forget,
(Howard:)tomorrow morning, you're
driving me to the dentist.
(Bernadette:)I have to take you?
(Howard:)You don't have to take me.
You get to take me.
(Bernadette:)Wait a minute.
Are you telling me
(Bernadette:)your mother usually takes you
to the dentist?
(Howard:)It's not weird.
(Howard:)There's lots of kids there
with their moms.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe this.
(Howard:)What? It's fun.
(Howard:)If I have no cavities,
(Howard:)afterwards,
we go out for a treat.
(Bernadette:)All right, Howard, let's get
something straight right now.
(Bernadette:)I'm not going
to be your mother.
(Howard:)Whoa, whoa, whoa!
(Howard:)Where did that come from?
Who's that?!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Is it a
sex criminal?!
(Howard:)Nobody wants to do
that to you, Ma!
Where were you?!
Didn't you read my email?!